[ GRUNTS ]
MAN:
Psst.
LEE [ IN CHINESE ]:
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SANG SHOUTS IN CHINESE ]
[ SPEAKS IN CHINESE ]
[ GUNSHOTS ]
[ SIRENS WAILING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ BOAT ENGINE CHUGGING ]
MAN:
Forgive me, Consul Han...
...but I believe we can ill afford
to lose men of your high character.
And speaking as a friend...
...who's fought side by side
with you for 15 years...
...I will sorely miss
the unshakable support...
...you've given
the Royal Hong Kong Police.
And so on behalf of all Brits...
...who have ever carried the shield
in Hong Kong, we shall miss you.
We wish you happiness...
...as you take up your new post
in the United States.
Ladies and gentlemen, Consul Han.
GUESTS:
Consul Han.
HAN:
Thank you, Thomas.
Now, you know Thomas is not going
to make this evening easy.
[ IN ENGLISH ]
Excuse me.
[ WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY ]
[ SPEAKS IN CHINESE ]
Commander Griffin...
...I am pleased to be able
to leave you and Hong Kong...
...with a special gift tonight.
Earlier this evening,
Detective Inspector Lee...
...and his special task force
have once and for all...
...crushed the Juntao criminal
organization and reclaimed artifacts...
...from 5000 years of China's heritage.
[ SPEAKS IN CHINESE ]
This is the kind of legacy I dreamt about.
Hong Kong forever.
To Hong Kong forever.
GUESTS:
Hong Kong forever.
[ GRUNTS ]
Soo Yung.
[ IN CHINESE ]
[ CAR HORN HONKS ]
MAN 1:
Stupid fool! Get the hell out of my way!
Man, are you crazy?
-Shoot!
MAN 2: You moron!
Clive, what's up, man?
-You're late.
-Huh?
You're late.
-I'm late?
-Yeah, you're late.
You're late, man. I've been waiting
in the back for over an hour.
-I was in the diner.
-Man, I told you in the back.
Think I would do this shit out front?
-I'm gonna get busted.
-You weren't in the diner.
I said in the back of the d―
It don't even matter.
I'm late, you late. Let's do this.
What's that, a gun?
Put that away.
How many people you killed this year?
-Stop it, man. Let's do it. Come on.
-Don't be late again.
I ain't gonna be late. Come on.
What we got?
Hoo-hoo.
That's tight. That's beautiful.
That's nice. What's that?
-That's C-4.
-That's C-4?
That's C-4.
-Oh, shit.
-What's the problem?
No problem. I been looking
everywhere for this shit.
Man, how the hell you find some C-4?
You don't know how you make me feel,
man. The Iraqis can't even get this shit.
-Where'd you get this from?
-It's a hot ticket.
CARTER: You don't know how happy
you made me.
You got what I want.
Let me go get that money, man.
Step away from the car.
Hey, officers.
OFFICER: Put your hands above your heads.
Just do it now.
CARTER: Ain't no problem here.
Why y'all messing with us for?
All right, take it easy.
-You don't wanna do that.
-Yes, I do.
-No, he don't. He's playing.
-No, I ain't playing.
-Yes, he is, officer.
-No, I'm not. I'm not playing!
-Drop the gun!
-He's just my cousin. We're just talking.
Get back in the car and leave.
Can't do that, buddy.
I'll blow his head all over the parking lot!
-Get in the car and buy some doughnuts!
CARTER: See? You made him mad.
Let me just talk to him. All right?
OFFICER 1: Hey!
OFFICER 2: Don't move!
All right. All right. Everything cool now.
He down. The gun down.
Now get back in the car and just leave.
-Put your hands on your head!
-Everything's cool, officer.
Do it now!
OFFICER 2:
My arm!
Didn't I tell you to get in the car?
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ CAR HORNS HONKING ]
Man, stop it! I got C-4 in the trunk!
Yeah!
Hoo-hoo.
Clive, guess what, man.
I forgot to tell you. I'm L.A.P.D.
You under arrest.
HAN:
Soo Yung, come on, we're gonna be late.
Let's go.
WOMAN:
Excuse me.
-What?
-Telephone. China.
[ SPEAKS IN CHINESE ]
Soo Yung, I love you. Have a nice day.
[ IN ENGLISH ]
Will you be home after school?
No.
I am going to pick you up myself.
[ SPEAKING IN CHINESE ]
-Bye.
[ IN CHINESE ]
[ IN ENGLISH ]
Hello?
[ PHONE LINE CLICKS ]
[ MARIAH CAREY'S "FANTASY" PLAYING
ON RADIO ]
[ SINGING ]
Oh, when you walk by every night
Talking sweet and looking fine
I get kinda hectic inside